http://www.theproutschool.org/about-us/privacy-policy

Apply  |   Donate  |   Virtual Tour  |  PlusPortals  I  Calendar
Applying To Prout
Life at Prout Life at ProutOur Catholic IdentityFall 2020School CalendarGuidance DepartmentCollege and Career CounselingStudent ActivitiesSchool StoreSchool CancellationsFor VolunteersAdmissions The Prout AdvantageThe Admissions ProcessTuition & Financial AssistanceFor Accepted StudentsFor TransfersInternational StudentsAcademics Academics at ProutIB ProgramCore CurriculumElectivesAcademic Support ServicesAP ProgramOur FacultyAthletics Athletics at ProutCrusader Athletic TeamsMeet Our Coaching StaffWinter 2020 SportsThe FieldClub Sport: SailingAthletic Hall of FameArts The Arts at ProutDanceMusicTheatreVisual ArtsUpcoming PerformancesGiving Giving to ProutSupporting the FieldWays to GiveThe Prout FundFundraising EventsAbout Us About Us Faculty/StaffAlumniContact Information & DirectionsProut School HistoryPublicationsCOVID-19
Privacy Policy
HomeAbout UsPrivacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy online. When you visit our site, we may collect personal information from you such as your name and e-mail address. Our third party hosting company will collect additional information such as the URL you came from, your IP address, your domain name, your browser type, the country and state where your server is located, and the pages that were viewed during your visit to our site. All this information is kept on a secure server to protect it from outside parties.
We do not sell or rent personal information to others. We use your information only for the limited purposes of sending you updates and useful information about our programs, promotional information, enhancing the site operation, for statistical purposes, and for overall systems administration.
We understand and respect the right to privacy.
About Us Faculty/StaffAlumniContact Information & DirectionsProut School HistoryPublications
